Zankhna Chudasama () Featured

Software Developer seeking roles in Software Development. I have 4+ years of experience working in a product based company as a software developer and 3+ years of experience in angular5+ versions. I have hands-on in Angular 7 and Angular 8.



Current Designation: Consultant

Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)

Current Company: Capgemini

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Developer, Software Engineering, Software Development, Full Stack Development, Project

Management, Change Management, Quality Assurance, Manual Testing, Requirement Gathering, Programming, JavaScript, Eclipse, Jenkins, jQuery, MySQL, Docker, Maven, JIRA

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

4+ years of experience working in a product-based company as a full stack developer

Experience in requirement analysis with product team, design, workflow architecture, development, manual testing, and maintenance of web-based applications

2+ years of experience in developing single page application using angular 5+ version and typescript

Working on angular 8 for more than 1 year

Experience on working with modules, components, services of angular

Extensively worked on developing REST based applications

Good understanding of RxJs/ReactiveX operators

Experienced in working with RxJs Store management system

Experienced in working with Azure search service and Azure Data factory

Worked extensively in agile development process

Experienced working with micro services

Experienced working with GIT branching and merging

Work Experience

Capgemini as Consultant Nov 2020 to Till Date

I am working as an Angular developer for product development

Exxat Systems as Software Developer

Jun 2016 to Oct 2020

STEPS (Student Training, Education & Placement System) is a product for American physical therapy and personal assistance colleges to place their students in their clinical sites for future medical practice.

Project 1: Patient log (November 2019 - current)

Team size: 5

Description: Currently, I am working on Patient log product which is used by medical student during their clinical practice. They can log patient details using this product. Directors/faculties of the college are using to review the log data of patients added by their student

Involved in designing the Angular modules and components to create one SAP

Worked on REST/Web API to create services and tested on postman

Bind response of service with angular template

Used Rxjs store management system to reduce API calls

Created Reports using Azure data factory

Project 2: Patient log Code Search (September 2019 - November 2019)

Team size: 1

Description: Medical students have to search diagnosis and procedure codes to submit patient?s

data. I have used Azure Cognitive search services to implement it. Roles & Responsibilities:

Designed document for every searchable code and store them into cosmos DB

Used azure search service and created required indexes.

Created angular page for effective search

Project 3: Admission Portal (June 2019 - September 2019)

Team size: 7 to 10

Description: This product is used by students to get admission in medical university. Roles & Responsibilities:

Designed angular application for this portal

Extensively worked on reactive forms

Project 4: CORE (November 2018 - April 2019)

Team size: 2 to 3

Description:CORE is used by the medical students to submit reports of vaccinations of various common diseases such as mumps, meals etc.

Roles & Responsibilities:

? Worked on angular dynamic forms and angular reactive forms Technologies and Tool: Angular 7, TypeScript

Project 5: STEPS ? Evaluation (September 2016 ? October 2018)

Team size: 5

Description: STEPS-Evaluation is used by clinical educators and directors to evaluate their students. It is a fully dynamic system which creates forms and makes evaluation of student from dynamic data and caters different configurable features and workflows as per their requirements with sudden changes.

Roles & Responsibilities:

I along with my team had created form-configuration tool to create evaluation forms. Tool is used by configuration analyst to create dynamic forms for students, faculties, and clinical directors.

Introduced Daily evaluation system: Student can log their daily activities using daily evaluation system

Added different control type like star rating, rating scale

Technologies and tools: MVC5, LINQ, MYSQL, Bootstrap, jQuery

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Gujarat Technological University, Gujarat in 2016

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Angular 5+, RxJs/ReactiveX, HTML	7	2019	1 Year(s)
jQuery, JSON, MS SQL, Cosmos DB		2020	4 Year(s)
Azure Search Service, Azure Data Factory		2019	1 Year(s)
MS Office, Word, Excel, PowerPoint		2020	4 Year(s)
Angular	8	2020	2 Year(s)
Angular		2020	4 Year(s)
TypeScript			4 Year(s)

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert			
Hindi	Expert			

Gujarati

Expert

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent / Temporary

Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time